export const questions = [
  {
    question:
      "1.What do you call a computer on a network that requests files from another computer.",
    a: "A client",
    b: "A host",
    c: "A router",
    d: "A web server",
    correct: "a",
  },
  {
    question:
      "2. Hardware devices that are not part of the computer system and are often added later to the system.",
    a: "Peripheral",
    b: "Clip art",
    c: "Highlight",
    d: "Execute",
    correct: "a",
  },
  {
    question:
      "3. The main computer that stores the files that can be sent to computer that are networked together is:",
    a: "Clip art",
    b: "Motherboard",
    c: "Peripheral",
    d: "File Server",
    correct: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "4. How can you catch a computer virus?",
    a: "Sending email messages",
    b: "Using a laptot during winter",
    c: "Opening email attachments",
    d: "Shoping online",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "5. Google (www.google.com) is a:",
    a: "Search Engine",
    b: "Number in math",
    c: "Directory of images",
    d: "Chat service on  the web",
    correct: "a",
  },
  {
    question: "6. Which is not an internet protocol?",
    a: "HTTP",
    b: "STP",
    c: "FTP",
    d: "IP",
    correct: "b",
  },
  {
    question: "7. Which of the following is not a valid domain?",
    a: "www.yahoo.com",
    b: "ww.yahoo.co.ku",
    c: "www.com.yahoo",
    d: "ww.yahoo.co.in",
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    question: "8. AOL stands for",
    a: "Arranged Outer Line",
    b: "American Over LAN",
    c: "Audio Over LAN",
    d: "American On-liner",
    correct: "d",
  },
  {
    question: "9. Another name for a computer chip is?",
    a: "Execute",
    b: "Micro chip",
    c: "Microprocessor",
    d: "Select",
    correct: "b",
  },
  {
    question: '10. "www" stands for:',
    a: "World Wide Web",
    b: "World Wide Wares",
    c: "World Wide Wait",
    d: "World Wide War",
    correct: "a",
  },
];
